

M stanli867@gmail.com | **८** 9487675545 | **1** stanli_In | **?** Nagercoil

SUMMARY STATEMENT

Web developer with 1.8 years of .NET experience and recently completed a MERN Full Stack Development course. Skilled in building and debugging web applications using React, Node js, MongDB, and .NET. Works effectively both independently and in teams.

SKILLS

FrontEnd Skills | React • JavaScript • HTML • CSS • Tailwind css • Bootstrap

BackEnd Skills | Node js • Express js

Database | MongoDB

Tools | Postman • GITHub

Soft Skills | Team player • Deliver results

EXPERIENCE

Lana Technologies Pvt Ltd. | C#, Asp.net web forms

July 2024 - Oct 2024 | Ernakulam, Kochi, Kerala.

- Worked on a gym application with full customization of existing functionalities and new feature development based on client requirements.
- Fixed payment receipt calculation issues reported by the client.Implemented
 GST-inclusive and GST-exclusive payment options.
- Added subscription plan extension functionality. Customized stored procedures and resolved bugs.

M-Squared Software & Services Pvt Ltd | C#, Asp.net mvc, .Net web api, Mssql.

Oct 2022 - Feb 2024 | TechnoPark, Trivandrum, Kerala.

- Worked on a gaming project. Developed and integrated project features by creating APIs using ASP.NET Web API and ASP.NET MVC5.
- Implemented UI and functionalities based on project requirements,
- Implemented user profiles, login, and registration form validation using JQuery.
- Implemented DataTransferObjects (DTO) for exposing only essential data in the API. Identified and resolved critical bugs in Projects, resulting in a 25% decrease in customer-reported issues and increased user satisfaction.

COURSEWORK & CERTIFICATION

GUVI Geek Networks, IITM Research Park | Dec 2024-present

MERN Full Stack Development

https://guvizenclass.in/certificate

Topics covered:

- HTML CSS Tailwind css JavaScript,
- React Redux
- Node js Express js MongoDB REST APIs
- Postman GitHub

PROJECT WORK

Online vehicle rental system Tech :

- React , Node js, Express, MongoDB
- StateManagement, contextAPI
- Bearer token
- Authentication & Authorization
- Node mailer
- stripe-payment

Live Demo | GitHub - FrontEnd & BackEnd

PORTFOLIO

• Visit: https://stanli.dev

QUALIFICATION

B.E Mechanical Engineering-2019
Udaya School Of Engineering
Nagercoil, TamilNadu | India.

LANGUAGE

English | Tamil | Malayalam

INTEREST

Fitness | Food | Self-Improvement